# Chitta Suresh

## Front-end Developer and Java Full stack Development

Front-end Developer with 1.7 Year of Experience in Creating and Developing Websites using Front-end Technologies. I'm having Analytical thinking, strong technical, problem solving skills and having knowledge of Front-end Technologies to excel as a Front-end developer. I'm seeking to get challenging position as a Front-end Developer Role.

chittasureshtech@gmail.com

+91 9611129217

32Main , Golden enclave, Poorna Pragna Nagara, Sandhya deepa ashrama Road,BWSSB Pump,Subramanya pura , Uttarahalli-560061, Bengaluru, India

linkedin.com/in/tech-chitta-suresh-691b94264

https://web.skype.com/?openPstnPage=true

github.com/Techchittasuresh1995



## WORK EXPERIENCE

## **Front-end Developer**

Reactz(Reformx)consulting pvt ltd

04/2021 - 11/2022

Reactz(Reformx) Consulting is a Web Development , Mobile Applications development & Staff Augmentation organization with a strong focus on Staffing solutions. Headquartered at Bangalore, India,

Achievements/Tasks

 REACTZ Consulting India Pvt Ltd # 11, Rekha Building, RV Road, Basavanagudi, Bangalore 560004 Website: WWW.REACTZ.TECH Email: HR@REACTZ.TECH Mob: 99161010077 / 9035559894

# **PROJECTS**

01.Responsive Personal Portfolio website using frontend technologies

 portfolio showing that "About me,education,work experience, Clients reviews,my work"

02. Responsive Realestate website using html,css,javascript

 Its a website in which number of homes are there. The client will sell the all homes to customers,

-----> For more projects, GitHub link is provided at above^.

# **EDUCATION**

# **Diploma in Engineering**

P.E.S polytechnic, Bangalore

06/2013 - 05/2016

Courses

Automobile Engineering

#### **HSC/Intermediate**

Vijaya college, R.V Road, Southend circle, Bengaluru 08/2010 - 04/2013

# SSC/10th

Z.P.highschool,chittoor,Andhra padesh

07/2000 - 07/2010

# SKILLS



# WORK EXPERIENCE/JOB DESCRIPTION

Design and code reviews to build applications and prototypes

Working with designers & product managers to build things in browser-based analytics applications

Working on the drive from conceptualization to the deployment of an analytics suite of products

Exploring & understanding the under-hood of products in the market, strengths & fault-lines of each

Proficient understanding of code versioning tools Git

Backend logics and give support to backend team

Building, designing, testing, and deploying web applications

Experience & Knowledge of how to dynamic pages creations

working with debugging tools like Firebug, Chrome inspector, etc.

#### INTERNSHIP TRAINEE

REFORMX Consulting (REACTZ Consulting Pvt Ltd), (10/2020 - 03/2021)